{"exercises": [{"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_en": "good morning", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "question": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_en": "good morning", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "sentence_en": "answer to \"good morning\"", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "question": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "sentence_en": "answer to \"good morning\"", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0633\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_en": "good evening", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "question": "\u0645\u0633\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0633\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_en": "good evening", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a", "sentence_en": "again, please", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a", "sentence_en": "again, please", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0648", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0648 \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "sentence_en": "please", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "question": "\u0644\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0648 \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "sentence_en": "please", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0627 \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d", "question": "\u062f\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0627 \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u062f\u0627 \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0627 \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640", "sentence_en": "Drop me off at ...", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640", "sentence_en": "Drop me off at ...", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0640\u0640\u0640", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640", "sentence_en": "Drop me off at ...", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0640\u0640\u0640", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640", "sentence_en": "Drop me off at ...", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": null, "wrong_answer": "\u0640\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "sentence_en": "Hello (basic greeting)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "salaam \u2018aleikum", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "question": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "sentence_en": "Hello (basic greeting)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "salaam \u2018aleikum", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u064a\u0632"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0639 \u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629", "sentence_en": "Goodbye", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ma\u2019a salaameh", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629", "question": "\u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0639 \u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629", "sentence_en": "Goodbye", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ma\u2019a salaameh", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u064a\u0647\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "How\u2019s it going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aamil eh?\nizzayak?\neh akhbaar?\nakhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "How\u2019s it going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aamil eh?\nizzayak?\neh akhbaar?\nakhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\n\u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "How\u2019s it going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aamil eh?\nizzayak?\neh akhbaar?\nakhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "How\u2019s it going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aamil eh?\nizzayak?\neh akhbaar?\nakhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "How\u2019s it going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aamil eh?\nizzayak?\neh akhbaar?\nakhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\n\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u064a\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "How\u2019s it going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aamil eh?\nizzayak?\neh akhbaar?\nakhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f\n\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f\n\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f\n\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "How\u2019s it going?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aamil eh?\nizzayak?\neh akhbaar?\nakhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "Fine\nEverything\u2019s good", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "kwayyis, kullu tamaam\nalHamdulillah", "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0644\u0647", "question": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "Fine\nEverything\u2019s good", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "kwayyis, kullu tamaam\nalHamdulillah", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "Fine\nEverything\u2019s good", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "kwayyis, kullu tamaam\nalHamdulillah", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0645\u0627\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f", "question": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "Fine\nEverything\u2019s good", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "kwayyis, kullu tamaam\nalHamdulillah", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647", "question": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "Fine\nEverything\u2019s good", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "kwayyis, kullu tamaam\nalHamdulillah", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0639\u062f", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_en": "Excuse me!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ba3d iznak (or iznik to a female)", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0639\u062f"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "question": "\u0628\u0639\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_en": "Excuse me!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ba3d iznak (or iznik to a female)", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627\u0644", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0633\u0650\u0641", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0633\u0650\u0641", "sentence_en": "Sorry (bumping into someone)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "l\u2019il asif", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633", "question": "\u0644\u0627\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u0650\u0641", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0633\u0650\u0641", "sentence_en": "Sorry (bumping into someone)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "l\u2019il asif", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0648", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0648 \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "sentence_en": "Pardon me", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "law samaHt", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "question": "\u0644\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0648 \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "sentence_en": "Pardon me", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "law samaHt", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u064a\u0632", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_en": "Excuse me, I want to tell you something", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3yiiz a\u2019ool lak ba3d iznak", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644", "question": "\u0639\u064a\u0632 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_en": "Excuse me, I want to tell you something", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3yiiz a\u2019ool lak ba3d iznak", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0643", "question": "\u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_en": "Excuse me, I want to tell you something", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3yiiz a\u2019ool lak ba3d iznak", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0639\u062f", "question": "\u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_en": "Excuse me, I want to tell you something", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3yiiz a\u2019ool lak ba3d iznak", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "question": "\u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_en": "Excuse me, I want to tell you something", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3yiiz a\u2019ool lak ba3d iznak", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0649", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0649 \u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649", "sentence_en": "Hey, driver!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ya usTa!", "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649", "question": "\u064a\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0649 \u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649", "sentence_en": "Hey, driver!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ya usTa!", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0636\u0631\u062a\u0643", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u062d\u0636\u0631\u062a\u0643", "sentence_en": "Officer/sir!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "HaDritak", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0629", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s this, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "eh dah min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0629", "question": "\u0627\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s this, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "eh dah min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646", "question": "\u0627\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s this, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "eh dah min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "question": "\u0627\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s this, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "eh dah min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0643\u0645", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u0643\u0645 \u062f\u0629", "sentence_en": "How much is this?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "bikam dah?", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0629", "question": "\u0628\u0643\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u0643\u0645 \u062f\u0629", "sentence_en": "How much is this?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "bikam dah?", "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u064a\u0632", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u064a\u0632", "sentence_en": "I want\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana 3ayiiz\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u064a\u0632", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u064a\u0632", "sentence_en": "I want\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana 3ayiiz\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_ar": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_en": "It\u2019s too expensive!\nIt\u2019s so much!\nI will pay\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ghaali \u2018awwi!\nktiir awwi!\nana badfa3\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a", "question": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_ar": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_en": "It\u2019s too expensive!\nIt\u2019s so much!\nI will pay\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ghaali \u2018awwi!\nktiir awwi!\nana badfa3\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631", "question": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_ar": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_en": "It\u2019s too expensive!\nIt\u2019s so much!\nI will pay\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ghaali \u2018awwi!\nktiir awwi!\nana badfa3\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a", "question": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_ar": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_en": "It\u2019s too expensive!\nIt\u2019s so much!\nI will pay\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ghaali \u2018awwi!\nktiir awwi!\nana badfa3\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_ar": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_en": "It\u2019s too expensive!\nIt\u2019s so much!\nI will pay\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ghaali \u2018awwi!\nktiir awwi!\nana badfa3\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "question": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a\n\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_en": "It\u2019s too expensive!\nIt\u2019s so much!\nI will pay\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ghaali \u2018awwi!\nktiir awwi!\nana badfa3\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u064a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0637\u064a\u0628\n\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u064a\n\u0637\u064a\u0628\n\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a", "sentence_en": "OK", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "maashi\ntayyib\ntamaam\nokey", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0637\u064a\u0628", "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u064a\n\u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u064a\n\u0637\u064a\u0628\n\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a", "sentence_en": "OK", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "maashi\ntayyib\ntamaam\nokey", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u064a\u0632"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u064a\n\u0637\u064a\u0628\n\u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u064a\n\u0637\u064a\u0628\n\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a", "sentence_en": "OK", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "maashi\ntayyib\ntamaam\nokey", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0645\u0627\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a", "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u064a\n\u0637\u064a\u0628\n\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u064a\n\u0637\u064a\u0628\n\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\n\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a", "sentence_en": "OK", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "maashi\ntayyib\ntamaam\nokey", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0649", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0649\u060c \u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_en": "Yes, of course/thank you", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "aywa, tab3an/shukran", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646", "question": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0649\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0649\u060c \u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_en": "Yes, of course/thank you", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "aywa, tab3an/shukran", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "question": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0649\u060c \u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646\\\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0649\u060c \u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_en": "Yes, of course/thank you", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "aywa, tab3an/shukran", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0627\u0633\u0641\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0633\u0641\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_en": "No, sorry/thank you", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "la, aasif/shukran", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0641", "question": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0633\u0641\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_en": "No, sorry/thank you", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "la, aasif/shukran", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "question": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0633\u0641\\\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0633\u0641\\\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_en": "No, sorry/thank you", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "la, aasif/shukran", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064b", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u064b", "sentence_en": "You\u2019re welcome", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "\u2018afwan", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I [please]?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "mumken [min faDlak]?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u062e\u062f \u0635\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u0646\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062e\u062f \u0635\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I take a photo here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "mumken akhud Surah hina?", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062e\u062f", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u0646\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062e\u062f \u0635\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I take a photo here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "mumken akhud Surah hina?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0648\u0631\u0629", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062e\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062e\u062f \u0635\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I take a photo here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "mumken akhud Surah hina?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062e\u062f \u0635\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062e\u062f \u0635\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I take a photo here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "mumken akhud Surah hina?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0647\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I look, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "mumken ashuuf min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I look, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "mumken ashuuf min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I look, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "mumken ashuuf min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I look, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "mumken ashuuf min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0646\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I go in from here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "momken adkhul min hina?", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0646\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I go in from here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "momken adkhul min hina?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I go in from here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "momken adkhul min hina?", "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I go in from here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "momken adkhul min hina?", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0628\u0633", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0628\u0633", "sentence_en": "I just want to look", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana 3ayiiz ashuuf bas", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u064a\u0632", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0628\u0633", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0628\u0633", "sentence_en": "I just want to look", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana 3ayiiz ashuuf bas", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u064a\u0632 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0633", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0628\u0633", "sentence_en": "I just want to look", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana 3ayiiz ashuuf bas", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0633", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641 \u0628\u0633", "sentence_en": "I just want to look", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana 3ayiiz ashuuf bas", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_en": "Thanks", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "shukran", "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062f\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0643\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0641 \u0634\u0643\u0631", "sentence_en": "A thousand thanks", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "alf shokr", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631", "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0641 \u0634\u0643\u0631", "sentence_en": "A thousand thanks", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "alf shokr", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0647\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this? / the Bathroom, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "fayn dah/il Hammaam, min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0647", "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this? / the Bathroom, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "fayn dah/il Hammaam, min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0647\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this? / the Bathroom, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "fayn dah/il Hammaam, min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u0647\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this? / the Bathroom, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "fayn dah/il Hammaam, min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646", "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u0647\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this? / the Bathroom, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "fayn dah/il Hammaam, min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643", "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u0647\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f\n\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this? / the Bathroom, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "fayn dah/il Hammaam, min faDlak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0631\u0648\u062d", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0632\u064a \u0643\u062f\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0632\u064a \u0643\u062f\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "I go this way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "baruuH zayy kida?", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0628\u0631\u0648\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0632\u064a", "question": "\u0628\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062f\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0632\u064a \u0643\u062f\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "I go this way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "baruuH zayy kida?", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062f\u0627", "question": "\u0628\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0632\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0632\u064a \u0643\u062f\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "I go this way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "baruuH zayy kida?", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0648\u0644", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0637\u0648\u0644", "sentence_en": "straight ahead", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3ala Tuul", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0648\u0644", "question": "\u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0637\u0648\u0644", "sentence_en": "straight ahead", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3ala Tuul", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0644\u0635", "question": "!\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "!\u062e\u0644\u0635", "sentence_en": "Finished!\nIt\u2019s over!\nI\u2019m done!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "khallaS!", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u062f\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u062f\u0647", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t need this", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "la, ana mish miHtaag dah", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u062f\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u062f\u0647", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t need this", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "la, ana mish miHtaag dah", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634", "question": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u062f\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u062f\u0647", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t need this", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "la, ana mish miHtaag dah", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c", "question": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u062f\u0647", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t need this", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "la, ana mish miHtaag dah", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0647", "question": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u062f\u0647", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t need this", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "la, ana mish miHtaag dah", "wrong_answer": "\u0622\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634 \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\\\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\\\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t know.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana mish 3aarif/3aarfa", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\\\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\\\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t know.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana mish 3aarif/3aarfa", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f\\\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\\\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t know.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana mish 3aarif/3aarfa", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\\\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\\\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t know.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana mish 3aarif/3aarfa", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0641\u0636", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u0651\u0640\u0644", "sentence_ar": "\u0625\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0651\u0640\u0644", "sentence_en": "Please go ahead!\nPlease sit!\nPlease take this!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "itfaDDal/itfaDDali", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0640\u0644", "question": "\u0625\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0651\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0625\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0651\u0640\u0644", "sentence_en": "Please go ahead!\nPlease sit!\nPlease take this!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "itfaDDal/itfaDDali", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "sentence_en": "Hello (peace upon you).", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Salaam \u2018aleikum.", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "question": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "sentence_en": "Hello (peace upon you).", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Salaam \u2018aleikum.", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0643\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0647\u0644\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0647\u0644\u0627", "sentence_en": "Welcome.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ahlan.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062e", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062e \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_en": "Good morning.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Saba7 elkheer.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "question": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062e \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062e \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_en": "Good morning.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Saba7 elkheer.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "sentence_en": "Good morning (response).", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Saba7 el noor.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "question": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "sentence_en": "Good morning (response).", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Saba7 el noor.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0621", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_en": "Good evening.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Massa elkheer.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "question": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631", "sentence_en": "Good evening.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Massa elkheer.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0621", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "sentence_en": "Good evening (response).", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Massa el noor.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "question": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631", "sentence_en": "Good evening (response).", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Massa el noor.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "How are you?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Izzayak / Izzayik?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u064a\u0647 / \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f / \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s up?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eh akhbaar? / Akhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f / \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s up?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eh akhbaar? / Akhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f / \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s up?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eh akhbaar? / Akhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647 / \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f / \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s up?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eh akhbaar? / Akhbaarak eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 / \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 / \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u0629", "sentence_en": "I am good.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana Kwayyis / kwayISSuh", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 / \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u0629", "sentence_en": "I am good.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana Kwayyis / kwayISSuh", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 / \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 / \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u0629", "sentence_en": "I am good.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana Kwayyis / kwayISSuh", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u0629", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 / \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 / \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u0629", "sentence_en": "I am good.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana Kwayyis / kwayISSuh", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0644\u0647", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645", "sentence_en": "Everything\u2019s great.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Kullu tamaamh.", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u0644\u0647 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645", "sentence_en": "Everything\u2019s great.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Kullu tamaamh.", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0645\u0627\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f\u0629.", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629 \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f\u0629.", "sentence_en": "Nice to meet you.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Forsa sa3eeda.", "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0631\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f\u0629", "question": "\u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f.", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629 \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f\u0629.", "sentence_en": "Nice to meet you.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Forsa sa3eeda.", "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0633\u0639\u062f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0627\u0633\u0639\u062f", "sentence_en": "Nice to meet you, as well.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana As3ad.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0639\u062f", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0627\u0633\u0639\u062f", "sentence_en": "Nice to meet you, as well.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana As3ad.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0641\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "Thanks be to God.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "alHamdulillah", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647", "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "Thanks be to God.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "alHamdulillah", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627", "sentence_en": "Thank you.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Shokran.", "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062f\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0643\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0641 \u0634\u0643\u0631", "sentence_en": "A thousand thanks.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Alf shokr.", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631", "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0641 \u0634\u0643\u0631", "sentence_en": "A thousand thanks.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Alf shokr.", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627", "sentence_en": "You\u2019re welcome.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3afwan.", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u064a\u0632"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0648", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0648 \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "sentence_en": "Pardon me \u2013 please.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Law sama7t.", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "question": "\u0644\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0648 \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a", "sentence_en": "Pardon me \u2013 please.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Law sama7t.", "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644\u064a. (   )", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644\u064a. (masculine followed by feminine)", "sentence_en": "Please go ahead.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Etfutdll / Etfutdlee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644\u064a", "question": "\u0627\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f. (   )", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644\u064a. (masculine followed by feminine)", "sentence_en": "Please go ahead.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Etfutdll / Etfutdlee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0639\u062f", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_en": "Excuse me.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ba3d izznuck / izznick.", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0639"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "question": "\u0628\u0639\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643", "sentence_en": "Excuse me.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ba3d izznuck / izznick.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0633\u0641\u0629.", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0633\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0633\u0641\u0629.", "sentence_en": "I am sorry.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana awsiff / awssfa.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0641", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u2013 \u0627\u0633\u0641\u0629.", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0633\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0633\u0641\u0629.", "sentence_en": "I am sorry.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana awsiff / awssfa.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0641\u0629", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0633\u0641 \u2013 \u061f\u061f\u061f.", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0633\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0633\u0641\u0629.", "sentence_en": "I am sorry.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana awsiff / awssfa.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a / \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0646\u064a ()", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a / \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0646\u064a (feminine)", "sentence_en": "Can you help me, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Momken tsa3dni / tsa3dini, law samht?", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0646\u064a ()", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a / \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0646\u064a (feminine)", "sentence_en": "Can you help me, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Momken tsa3dni / tsa3dini, law samht?", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a / \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0646\u064a ()", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a / \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0646\u064a (feminine)", "sentence_en": "Can you help me, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Momken tsa3dni / tsa3dini, law samht?", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0646\u064a", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a / \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f ()", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a / \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0646\u064a (feminine)", "sentence_en": "Can you help me, please?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Momken tsa3dni / tsa3dini, law samht?", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0634 \u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629", "sentence_en": "No problem!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mish mooshkela!", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629", "question": "\u0645\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0634 \u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629", "sentence_en": "No problem!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mish mooshkela!", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u062a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u061f", "sentence_en": "Do you know the way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta a3ruff / entee a3ruffuh altaree?", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u061f", "sentence_en": "Do you know the way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta a3ruff / entee a3ruffuh altaree?", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641 \u2013 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u061f", "sentence_en": "Do you know the way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta a3ruff / entee a3ruffuh altaree?", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u061f", "sentence_en": "Do you know the way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta a3ruff / entee a3ruffuh altaree?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u061f", "sentence_en": "Do you know the way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta a3ruff / entee a3ruffuh altaree?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u2013 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u2013 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t understand", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana mish fahem / fahmuh.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u2013 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u2013 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t understand", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana mish fahem / fahmuh.", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u2013 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u2013 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t understand", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana mish fahem / fahmuh.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u2013 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u2013 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u0629", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t understand", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana mish fahem / fahmuh.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0647\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_en": "I am learning Arabic.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana bawta3alm 3rabee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_en": "I am learning Arabic.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana bawta3alm 3rabee.", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_en": "I am learning Arabic.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana bawta3alm 3rabee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634 \u0628\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0628\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t speak Arabic.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mish betkelum 3rabee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0628\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t speak Arabic.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mish betkelum 3rabee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0628\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t speak Arabic.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mish betkelum 3rabee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0643\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0628\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634 \u0628\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_en": "I don\u2019t speak Arabic.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mish betkelum 3rabee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u2013 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0628\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u2013 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0628\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can you speak slowly?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin tetkehlim/ee bera7aw? (masculine followed by feminine \u201ccan you\u2026\u201d)", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u2013 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0628\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u2013 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0628\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can you speak slowly?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin tetkehlim/ee bera7aw? (masculine followed by feminine \u201ccan you\u2026\u201d)", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u2013 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u2013 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0628\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can you speak slowly?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin tetkehlim/ee bera7aw? (masculine followed by feminine \u201ccan you\u2026\u201d)", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u2013 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u2013 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0628\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can you speak slowly?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin tetkehlim/ee bera7aw? (masculine followed by feminine \u201ccan you\u2026\u201d)", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0629", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0629 \u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_en": "This is very expensive.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Daw 5awlee owee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a", "question": "\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0629 \u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_en": "This is very expensive.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Daw 5awlee owee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a", "question": "\u062f\u0629 \u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0629 \u063a\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_en": "This is very expensive.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Daw 5awlee owee.", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0629", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_en": "This is too much.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Daw kiteer owee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631", "question": "\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_en": "This is too much.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Daw kiteer owee.", "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062a\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a", "question": "\u062f\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0648\u064a", "sentence_en": "This is too much.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Daw kiteer owee.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_en": "I will pay\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana badfa3\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639", "sentence_en": "I will pay\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana badfa3\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0644\u0627\u0635", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u062e\u0644\u0627\u0635", "sentence_en": "I\u2019m finished \u2013 done.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Khalass!", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0627 \u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649", "sentence_en": "Hey driver!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ya usta!", "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649", "question": "\u064a\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0627 \u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649", "sentence_en": "Hey driver!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ya usta!", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0621", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a \u062c\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u064a \u062c\u064a", "sentence_en": "Next street.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Elshare3 elgaya.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a", "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u064a \u062c\u064a", "sentence_en": "Next street.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Elshare3 elgaya.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a", "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u064a \u062c\u064a", "sentence_en": "Next street.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Elshare3 elgaya.", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0648\u0644", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0637\u0648\u0644", "sentence_en": "Straight ahead.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3ala tool.", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0648\u0644", "question": "\u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0637\u0648\u0644", "sentence_en": "Straight ahead.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3ala tool.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u2013 \u0634\u0645\u0627\u0644.", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0645\u064a\u0646 \u2013 \u0634\u0645\u0627\u0644.", "sentence_en": "Left \u2013 right.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Yameen / shamel.", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0645\u0627\u0644", "question": "\u064a\u0645\u064a\u0646 \u2013 \u061f\u061f\u061f.", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0645\u064a\u0646 \u2013 \u0634\u0645\u0627\u0644.", "sentence_en": "Left \u2013 right.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Yameen / shamel.", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0643\u0627\u0631\u0629", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0643\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0643\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0628\u0643\u0645\u061f", "sentence_en": "How expensive is the ticket?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eltazkara bkam?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0643\u0645", "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0643\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0643\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0628\u0643\u0645\u061f", "sentence_en": "How expensive is the ticket?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eltazkara bkam?", "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0639\u0627\u0646 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0646.", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0639\u0627\u0646 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0646.", "sentence_en": "I am hungry/I am thirsty.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana ga3an / ana 3atschan.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0639\u0627\u0646", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0646.", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0639\u0627\u0646 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0646.", "sentence_en": "I am hungry/I am thirsty.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana ga3an / ana 3atschan.", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0639\u0627\u0646 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0646.", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0639\u0627\u0646 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0646.", "sentence_en": "I am hungry/I am thirsty.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana ga3an / ana 3atschan.", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0646", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0639\u0627\u0646 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f.", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0639\u0627\u0646 \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0646.", "sentence_en": "I am hungry/I am thirsty.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana ga3an / ana 3atschan.", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0631\u062a", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0631\u062a\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can I pay with a credit card?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Momken adfa3 belkart?", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062f\u0641\u0639", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0631\u062a", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0631\u062a\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can I pay with a credit card?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Momken adfa3 belkart?", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0631\u062a", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0631\u062a\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can I pay with a credit card?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Momken adfa3 belkart?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I enter here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin edkhol hena?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I enter here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin edkhol hena?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u062f\u062e\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I enter here?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin edkhol hena?", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u0629 \u0627\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u062f\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 / \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u0629 \u0627\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u062f\u0629", "sentence_en": "I want to buy this.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eyeizz / eyezuh ehshteree daw.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u0629", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 / \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u062f\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 / \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u0629 \u0627\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u062f\u0629", "sentence_en": "I want to buy this.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eyeizz / eyezuh ehshteree daw.", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 / \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 / \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u0629 \u0627\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u062f\u0629", "sentence_en": "I want to buy this.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eyeizz / eyezuh ehshteree daw.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0629", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 / \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u0629 \u0627\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 / \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u0629 \u0627\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u062f\u0629", "sentence_en": "I want to buy this.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Eyeizz / eyezuh ehshteree daw.", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u064a\u0647\u2026..\u0628\u0644 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u064a\u0647\u2026..\u0628\u0644 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u061f", "sentence_en": "What does\u2026.mean in Arabic?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ya3ni ay\u2026. bel 3rabi?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f\u2026..\u0628\u0644 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u064a\u0647\u2026..\u0628\u0644 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u061f", "sentence_en": "What does\u2026.mean in Arabic?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ya3ni ay\u2026. bel 3rabi?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0644", "question": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u064a\u0647\u2026..\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u064a\u0647\u2026..\u0628\u0644 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u061f", "sentence_en": "What does\u2026.mean in Arabic?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ya3ni ay\u2026. bel 3rabi?", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a", "question": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u064a\u0647\u2026..\u0628\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u064a\u0647\u2026..\u0628\u0644 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u061f", "sentence_en": "What does\u2026.mean in Arabic?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ya3ni ay\u2026. bel 3rabi?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u064a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u064a", "sentence_en": "My name is\u2026.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Esmee\u2026.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0649"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0646", "sentence_en": "I am from\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana men\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0646", "sentence_en": "I am from\u2026", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ana men\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u2026.\u0633\u0646\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a\u2026.\u0633\u0646\u0629", "sentence_en": "I am\u2026.years old.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3ndy\u2026..sinuh", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0646\u0629", "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a\u2026.\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a\u2026.\u0633\u0646\u0629", "sentence_en": "I am\u2026.years old.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3ndy\u2026..sinuh", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0647", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0647", "sentence_en": "Yes.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Aywa.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627", "sentence_en": "No.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "La2.", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0627\u062a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0627\u062a", "sentence_en": "Sometimes.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Sa3eht.", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0648\u0644", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0637\u0648\u0644", "sentence_en": "All the time.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3law tool.", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0648\u0644", "question": "\u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0637\u0648\u0644", "sentence_en": "All the time.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3law tool.", "wrong_answer": "\u0640\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0628\u062f\u0627\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0628\u062f\u0627\u0646", "sentence_en": "Never.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ebedehn.", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u0649", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0627\u0634\u0649", "sentence_en": "Ok.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Maashi.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645", "sentence_en": "Excellent.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Tamaam.", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0645\u0627\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0637\u064a\u0628", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0637\u064a\u0628", "sentence_en": "Alright.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Tayyib.", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0627\u0643\u064a\u062f", "sentence_ar": "\u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646 / \u0627\u0643\u064a\u062f", "sentence_en": "Of course.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Tawba3n / akeed.", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0639"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0643\u064a\u062f", "question": "\u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646 / \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u062a\u0628\u0639\u0646 / \u0627\u0643\u064a\u062f", "sentence_en": "Of course.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Tawba3n / akeed.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0628\u0631\u0648\u0643", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0628\u0631\u0648\u0643", "sentence_en": "Congratulations!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mabrook!", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u064a\u062f", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u064a\u0644\u0627\u062f \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0645\u064a\u0644\u0627\u062f \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f", "sentence_en": "Happy birthday!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3eed meelehd sa3eed!", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0627\u062f", "question": "\u0639\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0645\u064a\u0644\u0627\u062f \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f", "sentence_en": "Happy birthday!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3eed meelehd sa3eed!", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f", "question": "\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0645\u064a\u0644\u0627\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0645\u064a\u0644\u0627\u062f \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f", "sentence_en": "Happy birthday!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3eed meelehd sa3eed!", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0639\u062f"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0627\u0621 \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0625\u0646 \u0634\u0627\u0621 \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "God-willing.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "InSHAallah.", "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u0621", "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0625\u0646 \u0634\u0627\u0621 \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "God-willing.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "InSHAallah.", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647", "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0634\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0625\u0646 \u0634\u0627\u0621 \u0644\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "God-willing.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "InSHAallah.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0639 \u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629", "sentence_en": "Goodbye.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ma\u2019a salaameh.", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0639"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629", "question": "\u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0639 \u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645\u0629", "sentence_en": "Goodbye.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ma\u2019a salaameh.", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0628\u0633\u0648\u0637", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0628\u0633\u0648\u0637 \u0639\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643", "sentence_en": "Happy to see you.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mawbsoot 3lashane ashoofuck/fick.", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0646", "question": "\u0645\u0628\u0633\u0648\u0637 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0628\u0633\u0648\u0637 \u0639\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643", "sentence_en": "Happy to see you.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mawbsoot 3lashane ashoofuck/fick.", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643", "question": "\u0645\u0628\u0633\u0648\u0637 \u0639\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0628\u0633\u0648\u0637 \u0639\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643", "sentence_en": "Happy to see you.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mawbsoot 3lashane ashoofuck/fick.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 \u0627\u0648\u0631\u064a\u0628", "sentence_ar": "\u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 / \u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 \u0627\u0648\u0631\u064a\u0628", "sentence_en": "See you soon.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Hashoofuck /fick ooreyib.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 \u0627\u0648\u0631\u064a\u0628", "sentence_ar": "\u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 / \u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 \u0627\u0648\u0631\u064a\u0628", "sentence_en": "See you soon.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Hashoofuck /fick ooreyib.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0631\u064a\u0628", "question": "\u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 / \u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 / \u0647\u0634\u0648\u0641\u0643 \u0627\u0648\u0631\u064a\u0628", "sentence_en": "See you soon.", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Hashoofuck /fick ooreyib.", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u0643\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u064a\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "What is your name?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Esmak/ick eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "What is your name?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Esmak/ick eh?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u062a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u064a\u0646 (         )", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u064a\u0646\u061f (masculine \u201cyou\u201d and femine \u201cyou\u201d are first two words here)", "sentence_en": "Where are you from?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta / entee menane?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u064a\u0646 (         )", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u064a\u0646\u061f (masculine \u201cyou\u201d and femine \u201cyou\u201d are first two words here)", "sentence_en": "Where are you from?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta / entee menane?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u064a\u0646 (         )", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u064a\u0646\u061f (masculine \u201cyou\u201d and femine \u201cyou\u201d are first two words here)", "sentence_en": "Where are you from?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta / entee menane?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f (         )", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u064a\u0646\u061f (masculine \u201cyou\u201d and femine \u201cyou\u201d are first two words here)", "sentence_en": "Where are you from?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta / entee menane?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0646 \u2013 \u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f \u2013 \u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where do you live?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Sakin fane / sakina fane?", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u2013 \u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f \u2013 \u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where do you live?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Sakin fane / sakina fane?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646\u0629", "question": "\u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a\u0646 \u2013 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f \u2013 \u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where do you live?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Sakin fane / sakina fane?", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u2013 \u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f \u2013 \u0633\u0627\u0643\u0646\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where do you live?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Sakin fane / sakina fane?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0647", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0647 \u0643\u0645\u061f", "sentence_en": "What time is it?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Elsa3a kam?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0639\u062f"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0645", "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0647 \u0643\u0645\u061f", "sentence_en": "What time is it?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Elsa3a kam?", "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is the bathroom?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Fane el7mmam?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is the bathroom?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Fane el7mmam?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646\u0648 / \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 / \u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627 / \u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0648 / \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 / \u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627 / \u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can I have a menu/coffee/water/shisha?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin menu/awhuwu/maya/shisha?", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u0648", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 / \u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627 / \u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0648 / \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 / \u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627 / \u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can I have a menu/coffee/water/shisha?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin menu/awhuwu/maya/shisha?", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0648 / \u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627 / \u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0648 / \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 / \u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627 / \u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can I have a menu/coffee/water/shisha?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin menu/awhuwu/maya/shisha?", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0648 / \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 / \u061f\u061f\u061f / \u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0648 / \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 / \u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627 / \u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can I have a menu/coffee/water/shisha?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin menu/awhuwu/maya/shisha?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627", "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0648 / \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 / \u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627 / \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0648 / \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 / \u0645\u0627\u064a\u0627 / \u0634\u064a\u0634\u0627\u061f", "sentence_en": "Can I have a menu/coffee/water/shisha?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Moomkin menu/awhuwu/maya/shisha?", "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u062a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where are you?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta / entee fane?", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u2013 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where are you?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta / entee fane?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u062a \u2013 \u0627\u0646\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where are you?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Enta / entee fane?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f- \u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0627\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645- \u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0627\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u061f", "sentence_en": "Do you speak English?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Betkehlm/ee Englizee? (masculine followed by feminine \u201cdo you speak\u2026\u201d)", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0643\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a", "question": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645- \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645- \u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0627\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u061f", "sentence_en": "Do you speak English?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Betkehlm/ee Englizee? (masculine followed by feminine \u201cdo you speak\u2026\u201d)", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a", "question": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645- \u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645- \u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645\u064a \u0627\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u061f", "sentence_en": "Do you speak English?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Betkehlm/ee Englizee? (masculine followed by feminine \u201cdo you speak\u2026\u201d)", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "sentence_en": "Hello", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "salaam \u2018alei-kum", "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "question": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643\u0645", "sentence_en": "Hello", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "salaam \u2018alei-kum", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0622\u0647", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0622\u0647", "sentence_en": "Yes", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ah", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627", "sentence_en": "No", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "La'", "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u0641\u0648", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u064e\u0641\u0648", "sentence_en": "You're welcome", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Al afow", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0648", "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u064e\u0641\u0648", "sentence_en": "You're welcome", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Al afow", "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0644", "question": "\u062a\u0650\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u062a\u0650\u0633\u0644\u064e\u0645", "sentence_en": "Be safe (addressing a male)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Tes-lam", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0644", "question": "\u062a\u0650\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u0645\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u062a\u0650\u0633\u0644\u064e\u0645\u064a", "sentence_en": "Be safe (addressing a female)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Tes-lami", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0645\u064a", "question": "\u062a\u0650\u0633\u0644\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u062a\u0650\u0633\u0644\u064e\u0645\u064a", "sentence_en": "Be safe (addressing a female)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Tes-lami", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0628\u064a\u0628\u064a", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u062d\u0628\u064a\u0628\u064a", "sentence_en": "My dear (literally: My love)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ha-bibi", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u064e\u0633\u064e\u0644", "sentence_ar": "\u064a\u0627 \u0639\u064e\u0633\u064e\u0644", "sentence_en": "Hey, honey", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ya 3a-sal", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f \u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "How are you doing?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aa-mil eh? iz-zay-ak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f \u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "How are you doing?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aa-mil eh? iz-zay-ak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643", "question": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u064a\u0647\u061f \u0627\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f", "sentence_en": "How are you doing?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "3aa-mil eh? iz-zay-ak?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0630\u0646\u0643"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f", "sentence_en": "How are things? (Any updates?)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "eh El-akh-baar?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631", "question": "\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u061f", "sentence_en": "How are things? (Any updates?)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "eh El-akh-baar?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0633", "question": "\u0643\u064f\u0648\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u064e\u0645\u064e\u0627\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u064f\u0648\u064e\u064a\u0633 \u062a\u064e\u0645\u064e\u0627\u0645", "sentence_en": "Fine", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "kway-yis ta-maam", "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0645", "question": "\u0643\u064f\u0648\u064e\u064a\u0633 \u062a\u064e\u0645\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u064f\u0648\u064e\u064a\u0633 \u062a\u064e\u0645\u064e\u0627\u0645", "sentence_en": "Fine", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "kway-yis ta-maam", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u0645\u0652\u062f\u064f \u0644\u0650\u0644\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u064e\u0645\u0652\u062f\u064f \u0644\u0650\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "Thank God!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Al-hamdu-lillah", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0647", "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u064e\u0645\u0652\u062f\u064f \u0644\u0650\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u064e\u0645\u0652\u062f\u064f \u0644\u0650\u0644\u0647", "sentence_en": "Thank God!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Al-hamdu-lillah", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644", "question": "\u0645\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f\u0650\u0634", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u064e\u0639\u0644\u0650\u0634", "sentence_en": "Sorry (for a non-harmful incident)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ma'lish", "wrong_answer": "\u0640\u0644"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062d\u062a\u064a", "question": "\u0644\u064e\u0648 \u0633\u064e\u0645\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u064e\u0648 \u0633\u064e\u0645\u064e\u062d\u062a\u064a", "sentence_en": "Pardon me (addressing a female)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "law sa-ma-Hti", "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0647", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0647 \u0644\u064e\u0648 \u0633\u064e\u0645\u064e\u062d\u062a (  )", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u062f\u0647 \u0644\u064e\u0648 \u0633\u064e\u0645\u064e\u062d\u062a\u061f (addressing a male)", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s this, please? (addressing a male)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "eh dah law sa-ma-Ht?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u064a\u0648\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0647", "question": "\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064e\u0648 \u0633\u064e\u0645\u064e\u062d\u062a (  )", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u062f\u0647 \u0644\u064e\u0648 \u0633\u064e\u0645\u064e\u062d\u062a\u061f (addressing a male)", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s this, please? (addressing a male)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "eh dah law sa-ma-Ht?", "wrong_answer": "\u0622\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062d\u062a", "question": "\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u062f\u0647 \u0644\u064e\u0648 \u0633\u064e\u0645\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f (  )", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u064a\u0647 \u062f\u0647 \u0644\u064e\u0648 \u0633\u064e\u0645\u064e\u062d\u062a\u061f (addressing a male)", "sentence_en": "What\u2019s this, please? (addressing a male)", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "eh dah law sa-ma-Ht?", "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0648\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0623\u0648\u064a", "sentence_en": "Too much!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ki-tir aw-wi!", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0648\u064a", "question": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0623\u0648\u064a", "sentence_en": "Too much!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ki-tir aw-wi!", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0648\u064a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639", "question": "\u0645\u0650\u0634 \u0647\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0643\u0652\u062a\u064e\u0631 \u0645\u0650\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0650\u0634 \u0647\u064e\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0623\u0643\u0652\u062a\u064e\u0631 \u0645\u0650\u0646", "sentence_en": "I won't pay more than..", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mish had-fa3 ak-tar min\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0641\u0639"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0643", "question": "\u0645\u0650\u0634 \u0647\u064e\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u0652\u062a\u064e\u0631 \u0645\u0650\u0646", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0650\u0634 \u0647\u064e\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0623\u0643\u0652\u062a\u064e\u0631 \u0645\u0650\u0646", "sentence_en": "I won't pay more than..", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mish had-fa3 ak-tar min\u2026", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0648", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u0629\u060c \u0637\u064e\u0628\u0639\u064e\u0627\u064b", "sentence_ar": "\u0623\u064a\u0648\u064e\u0629\u060c \u0637\u064e\u0628\u0639\u064e\u0627\u064b", "sentence_en": "Yes, of course", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "aywa, tab-3an", "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u064a\u0632"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0639", "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0648\u064e\u0629\u060c \u0637\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u0627\u064b", "sentence_ar": "\u0623\u064a\u0648\u064e\u0629\u060c \u0637\u064e\u0628\u0639\u064e\u0627\u064b", "sentence_en": "Yes, of course", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "aywa, tab-3an", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0645\u064f\u0633\u062a\u064e\u062d\u064a\u0644", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0645\u064f\u0633\u062a\u064e\u062d\u064a\u0644", "sentence_en": "No, never", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "La, mos-ta-Hil", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0633\u062a", "question": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0645\u064f\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u062d\u064a\u0644", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0645\u064f\u0633\u062a\u064e\u062d\u064a\u0644", "sentence_en": "No, never", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "La, mos-ta-Hil", "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062a"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062d\u064a\u0644", "question": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0645\u064f\u0633\u062a\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0627\u060c \u0645\u064f\u0633\u062a\u064e\u062d\u064a\u0644", "sentence_en": "No, never", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "La, mos-ta-Hil", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0622\u062e", "question": "\u0645\u064f\u0645\u0652\u0643\u0650\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u064f\u062f \u0635\u064f\u0648\u0631\u0629", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u064f\u0645\u0652\u0643\u0650\u0646 \u0622\u062e\u064f\u062f \u0635\u064f\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I take a photo?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mom-ken a-khud Surah?", "wrong_answer": "\u0622\u0647"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0631\u0629", "question": "\u0645\u064f\u0645\u0652\u0643\u0650\u0646 \u0622\u062e\u064f\u062f \u0635\u064f\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u064f\u0645\u0652\u0643\u0650\u0646 \u0622\u062e\u064f\u062f \u0635\u064f\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f", "sentence_en": "May I take a photo?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mom-ken a-khud Surah?", "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0646\u0627", "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0633 \u0628\u064e\u062a\u0641\u064e\u0631\u0651\u064e\u062c", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u0633 \u0628\u064e\u062a\u0641\u064e\u0631\u0651\u064e\u062c", "sentence_en": "I just want to take a look", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana bas bat-far-rag", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0633", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u064e\u062a\u0641\u064e\u0631\u0651\u064e\u062c", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u0633 \u0628\u064e\u062a\u0641\u064e\u0631\u0651\u064e\u062c", "sentence_en": "I just want to take a look", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana bas bat-far-rag", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641", "question": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u0633 \u0628\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u0631\u0651\u064e\u062c", "sentence_ar": "\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u0633 \u0628\u064e\u062a\u0641\u064e\u0631\u0651\u064e\u062c", "sentence_en": "I just want to take a look", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "ana bas bat-far-rag", "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0629"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0646", "question": "\u0641\u0650\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u064e\u0647", "sentence_ar": "\u0641\u0650\u064a\u0646 \u062f\u064e\u0647\u061f", "sentence_en": "Where is this?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "fen dah?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0627", "question": "  \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0642\u0635\u064e\u0631 \u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642", "sentence_ar": "Is this \u062f\u0627 \u0623\u0642\u0635\u064e\u0631 \u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u061f", "sentence_en": "the shortest way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "da Aksar tareek?", "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062f\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u0635", "question": "  \u062f\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u0631 \u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642", "sentence_ar": "Is this \u062f\u0627 \u0623\u0642\u0635\u064e\u0631 \u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u061f", "sentence_en": "the shortest way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "da Aksar tareek?", "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u0644\u0635"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642", "question": "  \u062f\u0627 \u0623\u0642\u0635\u064e\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "Is this \u062f\u0627 \u0623\u0642\u0635\u064e\u0631 \u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u061f", "sentence_en": "the shortest way?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "da Aksar tareek?", "wrong_answer": "\u0637\u064a\u0628"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627\u0635", "question": "!\u062e\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "!\u062e\u064e\u0644\u0627\u0635", "sentence_en": "It\u2019s done!", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Kha-las", "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0634", "question": "\u0645\u064e\u0644\u064f\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064f\u0632\u064f\u0648\u0645", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u064e\u0644\u064f\u0648\u0634 \u0644\u064f\u0632\u064f\u0648\u0645", "sentence_en": "no need", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ma-losh lo-zoom", "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0645", "question": "\u0645\u064e\u0644\u064f\u0648\u0634 \u0644\u064f\u0632\u064f\u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u064e\u0644\u064f\u0648\u0634 \u0644\u064f\u0632\u064f\u0648\u0645", "sentence_en": "no need", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Ma-losh lo-zoom", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0645"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0648", "question": "\u062f\u0650\u061f\u061f\u061f\u064e\u0642\u062a\u0650\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0650\u0644\u0648\u064e\u0642\u062a\u0650\u064a", "sentence_en": "Now?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Del-wa'-ti?", "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0648"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0642\u062a", "question": "\u062f\u0650\u0644\u0648\u064e\u061f\u061f\u061f\u0650\u064a", "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0650\u0644\u0648\u064e\u0642\u062a\u0650\u064a", "sentence_en": "Now?", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Del-wa'-ti?", "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633"}, {"prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:", "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a\u0646\u0641\u063a", "question": "\u0645\u0650\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f", "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0650\u0634 \u0647\u064a\u0646\u0641\u063a", "sentence_en": "It won't work out", "dialect": "Egyptian", "transliteration": "Mish hay-yen-fa3", "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627"}]}